morgan evans

experience designer

Currently a Sr. Experience Designer for Adobe's digital imaging ecosystem. I've worked across all surfaces of creative imaging products as both a designer and engineer, and strive to make customer-facing technology more user-friendly and aesthetically pleasing in this world of information overload.

work experience

Adobe

Sr. Experience Designer

March 2020 - Present

Most recently working with the Photoshop CC team to help launch Photoshop on the web. Primary areas of focus are: E2E growth experiences, onboarding and learn, interoperability across our varying creative apps, and more.

Previously working with the Lightroom CC team on its community and collaboration features.

Experience Designer + Developer

Oct 2016 - March 2020

UX designer and front-end developer for a v1.0 web application. Technical skills included Elm, JavaScript, UX design, and user research. Additionally, hire and mentor the team's 2018/2019 interns.

Nordstrom

UX Design Intern

June - Aug 2016

Assist in redesigning the internal POS system and Nordstrom.com left navigation bar.

education

Haas School of Business, Berkeley Executive Education

Product Management Certificate Program

2020

The program combines the latest in Design Thinking with the best of the Haas MBA program, to prepare for a role understanding a customer's environment, designing customer experiences, boosting team performance, and mobilizing an organization.

University of Washington

B.S. Informatics (HCI) / Minor in French

2011 - 2016

Solid understanding of development, design principles and information management. Proficient with front end development and cross-platform user experience design.

contact

Denver, CO 425.577.9678 evansmorg@gmail.com

links

evansmorgan.com linkedin.com/in/evansmn github.com/mnevans

design

Web Design
Mobile Design
Interaction Design
Prototyping
User Research

programming

HTML / CSS JavaScript React

software

Adobe Creative Suite Microsoft Office Suite Adobe XD Github JIRA / Trello

misc

Product Management Mentorship Animation Photography Video Editing